Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Whose Secret=
=سر من=
=Episode 3= (Sealed Memories)
=الحلقة 3= (ذكريات مختومة)
Miss Lu.
السيدة لو.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
I am the master of this dream realm.
أنا سيد عالم الأحلام هذا.
This is my domain.
هذا هو نطاقي.
Don't you wish to be with your sister forever?
ألا ترغب في البقاء مع أختك إلى الأبد؟
I can return her to you.
أستطيع أن أعيدها إليك.
She can stay with you forever.
يمكنها البقاء معك إلى الأبد.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
What's your condition?
ما هي حالتك؟
Talking terms with a clever person
التحدث مع شخص ذكي
is simple.
إنه بسيط.
You must stay here forever.
يجب عليك البقاء هنا إلى الأبد.
Everything here
كل شيء هنا
is nothing but a false dream.
ليس إلا حلما كاذبا.
What right do you have to bargain with me?
ما هو الحق الذي لديك في المساومة معي؟
You deceive humans, trapping them in your dream.
أنت تخدع البشر، وتوقعهم في فخ أحلامك.
Do you really think I'm that easy to fool?
هل تعتقد حقا أنني من السهل خداعي؟
False?
خطأ شنيع؟
Everything here may be an illusion,
كل شيء هنا قد يكون وهمًا،
but the warmth
ولكن الدفء
feels so real.
أشعر أن الأمر حقيقي جدًا.
It's far better than that hypocritical, broken world outside.
إنه أفضل بكثير من ذلك العالم الخارجي المنافق والمكسور.
I once had a sister too.
لقد كان عندي أخت أيضاً.
But unlike you,
ولكن على عكسك،
my sister
أختي
enslaved me,
استعبدني
destroyed me,
دمرني
and for a few pieces of silver,
ولبعض القطع الفضية،
she made me please those filthy men.
لقد جعلتني أُرضي هؤلاء الرجال القذرين.
In some ways,
في بعض النواحي،
I envy you a little.
أنا أحسدك قليلا.
If I had a sister like yours,
لو كان عندي أخت مثلك،
I wouldn't have needed to create a world like this
لم أكن بحاجة إلى إنشاء عالم مثل هذا
to deceive myself.
لأخدع نفسي.
But it doesn't matter.
ولكن لا يهم.
The warmth you once had,
الدفء الذي كان لديك ذات يوم،
I will have it all in this world.
سأحصل على كل شيء في هذا العالم.
And I'll keep you here forever
وسأبقيك هنا إلى الأبد
with me,
معي
until death.
حتى الموت.
I'll take your life right now.
سأقتلك الآن.
You try to trap humans in your dream realm,
تحاول اصطياد البشر في عالم أحلامك،
but in truth,
ولكن في الحقيقة،
you're the one who's trapped.
أنت الشخص المحاصر.
I just want them to stay with me.
أريد فقط أن يبقوا معي.
I want false happiness.
أريد سعادة كاذبة.
I don't want lonely suffering.
لا أريد أن أعاني وحيدًا.
To keep the Lord of Wujian trapped in the dream realm
للحفاظ على سيد ووجيان محاصرًا في عالم الأحلام
is my greatest honor.
هو أعظم شرف لي.
Stay.
يقضي.
Stay and share this endless loneliness with me.
ابقى وشارك هذه الوحدة التي لا نهاية لها معي.
Stay.
يقضي.
Li Motong.
لي موتونج.
I don't need your protection.
لا أحتاج إلى حمايتك.
Stay.
يقضي.
The demonic strings of this dream
الأوتار الشيطانية لهذا الحلم
will shatter you to pieces.
سوف يحطمك إلى قطع.
Even so,
ومع ذلك،
I don't want you to protect me.
لا أريدك أن تحميني.
To die within the dream realm
الموت في عالم الأحلام
or to live and leave it,
أو أن تعيش وتتركها،
which will you choose?
أيهما ستختار؟
(It's the Mei pearl.)
(إنها لؤلؤة مي.)
(The Mei pearl is inside her.)
(لؤلؤة مي موجودة بداخلها.)
(Li Motong,)
(لي موتونج،)
(Wujian will never let you go!)
(ووجيان لن يسمح لك بالرحيل أبدًا!)
(The Mei pearl truly lies within you.)
(لؤلؤة مي تكمن حقا في داخلك.)
(You're Lanyue.)
(أنت لانيو.)
(At dawn I watch the sky, at dusk the clouds,)
(عند الفجر أراقب السماء، وعند الغسق أراقب السحب)
(thinking of you as I walk,)
(أفكر فيك وأنا أمشي)
(thinking of you as I sit.)
(أفكر فيك وأنا جالس.)
(Li Motong,)
(لي موتونج،)
(I wish to stay by your side in this life.)
(أتمنى البقاء بجانبك في هذه الحياة.)
(Lanyue,)
(لانيو،)
(I've searched for you for a hundred years,)
(لقد بحثت عنك لمدة مائة عام)
(and I've finally found you.)
(و أخيرا وجدتك.)
♪You don't speak, I don't ask♪
♪أنت لا تتكلم، أنا لا أسأل♪
(I won't let you leave me again.)
(لن أسمح لك بتركني مرة أخرى.)
♪Behind falsehood lies truth♪
♪وراء الباطل تكمن الحقيقة♪
♪On the stage, beneath the heavens♪
♪على المسرح، تحت السماء♪
♪The soul runs free♪
♪الروح تنطلق بحرية♪
♪Boiled by fire, burned by water♪
♪مُسْلَكٌ بِالنَّارِ، مُحْرُوقٌ بِالْمَاءِ♪
(Who are you really?)
(من أنت حقا؟)
Lanyue.
لانيو.
♪The most beautiful, the most painful♪
♪الأجمل والأكثر إيلامًا♪
I've finally found you.
لقد وجدتك أخيرا.
♪I need no approval from you♪
♪لا أحتاج إلى موافقة منك♪
(What are you going to do?)
(ما كنت تنوي القيام به؟)
(Why do I always feel such an irresistible pull toward him?)
(لماذا أشعر دائمًا بجاذبية لا تقاوم نحوه؟)
(Let go of me.)
(اتركني)
♪A rose blooms upon my chest♪
♪تزهر الوردة على صدري♪
(Let me go.)
(دعني أذهب.)
♪A sudden sound, a mirrored panic♪
♪صوت مفاجئ، ذعر معكوس♪
♪A face I can no longer remember♪
♪وجه لم أعد أستطيع تذكره♪
♪The decayed scent, another dream embraced♪
♪الرائحة المتحللة، حلم آخر تم احتضانه♪
♪My red lips, your beating heart♪
♪شفتاي الحمراء، قلبك النابض♪
♪Meet at the edge of desire♪
♪الالتقاء على حافة الرغبة♪
No.
لا.
She's actually Lanyue.
إنها في الواقع لانيو.
You can't fall in love with her.
لا يمكنك أن تقع في حبها.
You can't repeat the same mistake.
لا يمكنك تكرار نفس الخطأ.
No.
لا.
I'll kill her.
سأقتلها
It's the Mei pearl.
إنها لؤلؤة مي.
The Mei pearl has been awakened again.
لقد استيقظت لؤلؤة مي مرة أخرى.
Where am I?
أين أنا؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
This is my home.
هذا هو بيتي.
It's safe.
إنه آمن.
What about your wounds?
ماذا عن جروحك؟
Things from the dream realm
أشياء من عالم الأحلام
don't come into reality.
لا تأتي إلى الواقع.
In the dream realm earlier,
في عالم الأحلام في وقت سابق،
we had to work together
كان علينا أن نعمل معًا
to escape.
للهروب.
But it was your people who killed my sister.
لكن شعبك هو الذي قتل أختي.
I can never side with you.
لا أستطيع أن أقف إلى جانبك أبدًا.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
It's because of you
إنه بفضلك
that we escaped the dream realm.
أننا هربنا من عالم الأحلام.
Because of me?
بسببي؟
(I can't let you get caught in Wujian's conflict again.)
(لا أستطيع أن أسمح لك بالتورط في صراع Wujian مرة أخرى.)
(I can't tell her.)
(لا أستطيع أن أخبرها.)
Nothing.
لا شئ.
As you said,
كما قلت
it was good cooperation.
لقد كان تعاونا جيدا.
Who are you, really?
من أنت حقا؟
I think we're friends.
أعتقد أننا أصدقاء.
We can't be friends.
لا يمكننا أن نكون أصدقاء.
Next time we meet,
في المرة القادمة التي نلتقي فيها،
we'll be enemies.
سوف نكون اعداء
I'll never be your enemy.
لن أكون عدوك أبدًا.
I'll protect you.
سأحميك.
I'll keep you safe from the demons.
سأحميك من الشياطين.
(Lanyue,)
(لانيو،)
(our fate was unfinished in the past life,)
(مصيرنا لم يكتمل في الحياة الماضية)
(this life I'll protect you completely.)
(في هذه الحياة سأحميك بالكامل.)
The Mei pearl's power destroyed the dream disc.
قوة لؤلؤة مي دمرت قرص الحلم.
It seems their destined fate cannot be escaped.
يبدو أن مصيرهم المحتوم لا يمكن الهروب منه.
According to Wujian's rules,
وفقا لقواعد Wujian،
once the Mei pearl reappears, it must return to Wujian.
بمجرد ظهور لؤلؤة مي مرة أخرى، يجب أن تعود إلى ووجيان.
What do you intend to do?
ماذا تنوي أن تفعل؟
I'll kill her
سأقتلها
and take back the Mei pearl.
واستعادة لؤلؤة مي.
Killing a human being.
قتل إنسان.
Do you wish to face heavenly punishment?
هل ترغب في مواجهة العقاب السماوي؟
The order of Wujian cannot be broken.
لا يمكن كسر نظام Wujian.
We
نحن
cannot interfere with human life and death at will.
لا يجوز التدخل في حياة الإنسان وموته بإرادته.
Moreover,
علاوة على ذلك،
the Mei pearl must be handled by Li Motong himself.
يجب أن يتم التعامل مع لؤلؤة مي بواسطة لي موتونغ بنفسه.
Even without breaking Wujian's law,
حتى بدون كسر قانون ووجيان،
the Mei pearl must still return to Wujian.
لا يزال يتعين على لؤلؤة مي أن تعود إلى ووجيان.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'll find a way.
سأجد طريقة.
Wait for my good news.
انتظر اخباري الجيدة.
(Li Motong,)
(لي موتونج،)
(is this truly)
(هل هذا حقا)
(your fate?)
(مصيرك؟)
=Whose Secret=
=سر من=
♪Her long hair with the dark night♪
♪شعرها الطويل مع الليل المظلم♪
♪Looks so pure in the lamplight♪
♪يبدو نقيًا جدًا في ضوء المصباح♪
♪Blurred flesh and tears♪
♪لحم مشوش ودموع♪
♪The evil spirit's hand pushes her into a kiss upon the rail♪
♪يد الروح الشريرة تدفعها إلى قبلة على السور♪
♪Where does the truth pretend to sleep?♪
♪أين تتظاهر الحقيقة بالنوم؟♪
♪Perfect last words confront what cannot be faced♪
♪الكلمات الأخيرة المثالية تواجه ما لا يمكن مواجهته♪
♪The scent corroded by the dawn♪
♪الرائحة المتآكلة بالفجر♪
♪Is her hollow soul tossed within a bottle♪
♪هل روحها المجوفة ملقاة داخل زجاجة♪
♪Bloodless lips bloom into bright petals♪
♪شفاه بلا دم تتفتح في بتلات مشرقة♪
♪Whispering their filthy confession♪
♪همس اعترافهم القذر♪
♪A white cat intently licks the thick sweet scent of blood♪
♪قطة بيضاء تلعق باهتمام رائحة الدم الحلوة الكثيفة♪
♪Accusing, demanding♪
♪متهم، متطلب♪
♪Who are you, who am I?♪
♪من أنت، من أنا؟♪
♪How did everything turn against itself?♪
♪كيف انقلب كل شيء ضد نفسه؟♪
♪What is striking inside the cold coffin?♪
♪ما هو الملفت للنظر داخل التابوت البارد؟♪
♪The restless bones beneath♪
♪العظام المضطربة في الأسفل♪
♪To which gravestone point her broken fingers♪
♪إلى أي شاهد قبر تشير أصابعها المكسورة♪
♪Who trembles, who grieves?♪
♪من يرتجف، من يحزن؟♪
♪Who is guiltless, who bears sin?♪
♪من هو البريء، من يتحمل الخطيئة؟♪
♪Take me to unearth redemption and fearlessness♪
♪خذني إلى اكتشاف الفداء والشجاعة♪
♪He kisses her fingertips♪
♪يقبل أطراف أصابعها♪
♪Bare joints blooming white iris♪
♪المفاصل العارية تتفتح زهور السوسن البيضاء♪
♪Nightmares and roses lie asleep♪
♪الكوابيس والورود نائمة♪
♪Nothing but a date with death♪
♪لا شيء سوى موعد مع الموت♪